emule.com 2001-08-12

# privacy

**eMule.com Privacy Policy**

* * *

This privacy policy is intended for those visiting eMule.com and affiliated sites. Our roster of current, past and future web projects. 

The Royal Archive &ndash; <http://www.royalarchive.com/>   
The Poetry Archive &ndash; <http://www.emule.com/poetry/>   
The Kyle Downes Page &ndash; <http://www.kyledownes.com/>   
The Price Index &ndash; <http://www.priceindex.org/>   
Aaron&rsquo;s Currency Page &ndash; <http://www.gilmer.net/currency/>   
Remote Linux &ndash; <http://www.remotelinux.com/>

Internet user privacy and confidentiality is of the utmost importance to eMule.com. Our reputation as a fun educational learning environment is directly related to how we serve our customers. Please find below a description of how eMule.com strives to protect the privacy of Internet users, and maintain the Internet as a highly credible medium. 

**Banner Advertising**

eMule.com and affiliated sites use BurstMedia as our representative to rotate banner advertising. Burst may use cookies to temporarily store information on your computer which may include information such as the number of times you have visited a specific website or loaded a page within a certain time frame. For more information on BurstMedia and their privacy policy (on which we have loosely based our own policy) please view this page: 

<http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp>

If you have any questions about BurstMedia or their privacy statement please email us: [emule@emule.com](mailto:emule@emule.com). 

**Links**

This web site may contain links to other sites. This statement is for the sole use and purpose of eMule.com and affiliated sites. Please be aware that eMule.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy practices of each and every web site before using the services provided. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes forums available to you. Please be aware, that whenever you post personal information online, through chat rooms, message boards, or email that this information can be collected and used by others. We will take all reasonable precautions to protect your privacy, but always keep in mind that when you are in a public forum, you control the information you disclose. 

**Surveys**

BurstMedia is our survey providor as well. They use a third party vendor to independently collect and archive this data which may be provided to potential advertisers to help target banner advertising. No personal information is obtained. The survey will continue to remain completely anonymous. Limited security may be employed in order to prevent individuals from taking the survey more than once. For more information you can email us at [emule@emule.com](mailto:emule@emule.com) or view the BurstMedia privacy statement: 

<http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp>

**Security**

This web site takes every reasonable precaution to protect our users' information.When you submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and offline. eMule.com has put security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alterations of the information under our control. Users may request that we delete all references (online and off) by corresponding with us at [emule@emule.com](mailto:emule@emule.com). 

**Disclosure**

eMule.com openly volunteers its practices of collecting information and its use of cookies. If you have any questions pertaining to this privacy policy and its contents, please direct your correspondence to [emule@emule.com](mailto:emule@emule.com). 

eMule.com reserves the right to change our policy from time to time. A revised policy will apply to information collected after the date the policy is changed.
